screen/skriːn/] the flat surface at the front of a television, computer, or other electronic device, on which you see pictures or information.
computer screen
a monitor with a 21 inch screen
They were staring at the television screen.
Move your cursor to the top of the screen.
the screen display
Can you do a printout of this screen for me (= of all the information on it)?
///////////////////////
màn

Động Từ
che bằng bình phong, che bằng màn, che chở, đem chuyện quay thành phim
Danh Từ
màn, màn ảnh, màn bạc chiếu bóng, màn che chụp ảnh, minh tinh màn bạc, tấm bình phong, vật che khuất