fixed  /fikst/ staying the same ,not changing or able to be changed.
fixed prices.
a fixed rate of interest.
Idioms
how are you, etc. fixed (for something)?
(informal) used to ask how much of something a person has, or to ask about arrangements
How are you fixed for cash?
How are we fixed for Saturday (= have we arranged to do anything)?
///
đã sửa

Tính Từ
bất biến, không thay đổi, nhất định, sửa lại