throw/θroʊ/to send something from your hand through the air by moving your hand or arm quickly=send something from hand, drop something carelessly 
Example.
 Stop throwing stones at the window!
She threw the ball up and caught it again.
Don't throw it to him, give it to him!
//
[transitive] throw something + adv./prep. to put something in a particular place quickly and carelessly
Just throw your bag down over there.