grass / /ɡræs/ /a common wild plant with narrow green leaves and stems that are eaten by cows, horses, sheep, etc.
The dog came running through the long grass
Keep off the grass
Don't walk on the grass.
//idom
put somebody out to grass
(informal) to force somebody to stop doing their job, especially because they are old
a snake (in the grass)
(disapproving) a person who pretends to be your friend but who cannot be trusted