spoil//spɔɪl//spoil something to change something good into something bad, unpleasant, useless, etc.= impair something (làm hỏng ,suy yếu)
Example.
Don't let him spoil your evening.
Don’t let the bad weather spoil your trip.
He spoils the children with expensive toys.
I don’t want to spoil things for everyone else.
Why do you always have to spoil everything?
////IDom
be spoiling for a fight
to want to fight with somebody very much.
too many cooks spoil the broth
(saying) if too many people are involved in doing something, it will not be done well.
///
cướp bóc,làm hỏng

Động Từ
cướp bóc, cướp phá, làm hư hàng hóa
Danh Từ
chiến lợi phẫm, đồ lấy được