jacket/ˈdʒækɪt/a piece of clothing worn on the top half of the body over a shirt, etc. that has sleeves and fastens down the front; a short, light coat.
She shrugged her shoulders into her jacket.
He wore a tweed sports jacket.
Áo khoác

Động Từ
đánh người nào một trận, mặc áo ngoài, xếp văn kiện vào bìa
Danh Từ
áo jacket, da loài cầm thú, lông loài cầm thú, vỏ trái cây, áo mặc ngoài, áo nịt ngoài của đàn bà, áo vét tông, cái bìa ngoài